radio.co 2019-12-08

# Privacy Policy | Radio.co

Last modified: 30th April 2018

* * *

## Radio.co Respects Your Privacy

This Policy explains when and why we collect personal information about people who visit our website or web application, how we use it, the conditions under which we may disclose it to others and how we keep it secure.

We may change this Policy from time to time so please check this page occasionally to ensure that you’re happy with any changes. By using our website or web application, you’re agreeing to be bound by this Policy.

Any questions regarding this Policy and our privacy practices should be sent by email to [help@radio.co](mailto:help@radio.co).

## What Personal Data Do We Collect?

**Personal Data You Provide to Us Voluntarily** – We collect information about you that you voluntarily provide to us when you: (i) contact us to learn more about Radio.co, Subscribe to a mailing list or other opportunities you indicate are of interest at the time; (ii) access or use Radio.co's Services ([studio.radio.co](https://studio.radio.co/)); or (iii) contact customer service. This information may include, for example, your name, business name, and any other information that you choose to provide to us when you comment on materials on our Radio.co Services, in order to contact you as a potential customer, or respond to a support request. This also includes technical data, such as IP addresses and device identifiers that are commonly generated in establishing a connection with the Radio.co Services. Payment information collected is processed securely by our Payment processor and is not stored in Radio.co's databases. This is bound by our processors privacy policy and will not be passed on to third parties under any circumstances.

**Other Data** \- By using the Radio.co services we may store information about what pages have been visited and when. This is to help us improve the usability of our services. 

**Retention** – We collect and retain Personal Data submitted to Radio.co in an identifiable format for the amount of time necessary to meet your request or fulfil our legal or regulatory obligations, unless it is in our legitimate business interests and not prohibited by law to maintain the Personal Data for longer periods.

## How Do We Process Personal Data?

We may use information for our legitimate interests, namely:

  * To operate the Radio.co Services.
  * To contact and communicate with you when you reach out to us to ask us about our Radio.co Services.
  * To manage everyday business needs.
  * To analyze or improve the Radio.co Services or additional products or services.
  * To protect the Radio.co Services and the rights of Users and others to enforce the terms of the Radio.co Services.
  * To comply with our obligations, including to comply with all applicable laws and regulations.
  * To send you promotional materials from us or on behalf of our affiliates and business partners if you have consented to the receipt of such materials.

## Who Has Access to Your Information?

Under no circumstances will we directly disclose or sell your personal information to any third party without your prior permission. We are strongly against any form of internet 'spam' and keep all collected information strictly confidential in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR).

We will not sell or provide your information to third parties for marketing purposes. 

## Third Party Services Working on Our Behalf

We may pass your information to our third party service providers, or other associated organisations for the purposes of completing tasks and providing services to you on our behalf (for example processing payments and providing sales/technical support). However, when we use third party service providers, we disclose only the personal information that is necessary to deliver the service and we have a contract in place that requires them to keep your information secure and not to use it for their own direct marketing purposes. 

Please be reassured that we will not release your information to third parties beyond the [Radio.co](https://radio.co/) network for them to use for their own direct marketing purposes, unless you have requested us to do so, or we are required to do so by law, for example, by a court order or for the purposes of prevention of fraud or other crime.

When you are using our secure online payment system, your payment is processed by a third party processor, who specialises in the secure online capture and processing of credit/debit card and PayPal transactions. If you have any questions regarding secure transactions, please contact us.

Radio.co's infrastructure is managed by multiple service providers (For example, Amazon Web Services). However they do not have access to any personal information and are prohibited to selling or passing on any stored data. 

## Security and Your Data

We take data security very seriously. Our databases are backed up regularly, and any data collected from you is sent over an encrypted SSL secure connection. Security of our data is important to us and we take every possible reasonable measure to prevent against loss, damage, theft or misuse where possible.

Any data processed by one of the third parties working on our behalf is also sent over an encrypted SSL connection. Third parties are contracted to provide a high level of security on their systems.

## Use of Cookies

Like many other websites, the Radio.co website uses cookies. 'Cookies' are small pieces of information sent by an organisation to your computer and stored on your hard drive to allow that website to recognise you when you visit. They collect statistical data about your browsing actions and patterns and do not identify you as an individual. For example, we use cookies to store your login preferences. This helps us to improve our website and deliver a better more personalised service.

It is possible to switch off cookies by setting your browser preferences. For more information on how to switch off cookies on your computer, visit our full cookies policy. Turning cookies of may result in a loss of functionality when using our website.

## Links to Other Websites

Our website, help centre and web application may contain links to other websites run by other organisations. This privacy policy applies only to our services‚ so we encourage you to read the privacy statements on the other websites you visit. We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other sites even if you access them using links from our website. In addition, if you linked to our website from a third party site, we cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of the owners and operators of that third party site and recommend that you check the policy of that third party site.

## Transferring Your Information Outside of Europe

As part of the services offered to you through this website, the information which you provide to us may be transferred to countries outside the European Union (“EU”). By way of example, this may happen if any of our servers are from time to time located in a country outside of the EU. These countries may not have similar data protection laws to the UK. By submitting your personal data, you’re agreeing to this transfer, storing or processing. If we transfer your information outside of the EU in this way, we will take steps to ensure that appropriate security measures are taken with the aim of ensuring that your privacy rights continue to be protected as outlined in this Policy. If you use our services while you are outside the EU, your information may be transferred outside the EU in order to provide you with those services.

## Website Recording 

Our web application and website use Analytics services provided by Google Analytics and Heap. Information collected from these services is entirely anonymous. Only general information is captured (For example, the type of browser or operating system you are using, screen resolution and which parts of the site you interact with). No form data is captured or read by these services. We use website recording services in order to improve our services’ usability and see how visitors interact with features and pages.  

## Legal

Radio.co (UK) Limited is registered with the Information Commissioners Office in compliance with UK law. Our Registration Number is: 9272479.

All customer data is handled sensitively by members of our team and physical access to our offices is restricted to authorised personnel only. 

Radio.co reserves the right to make alterations to this document whenever we deem reasonable. It is the clients sole responsibility to check this document for updates on a regular basis.  

## What Are Your Rights?

If at any point you believe the information we process on you is incorrect you can request to see this information and even have it corrected or deleted.

Please be aware, in order to remove any of your data this may prevent us from providing services to you and could result in the closure of your account. 

If you have any concerns regarding the data we hold on you, please contact us at [help@radio.co](mailto:%20help@radio.co)

Radio.co (UK) Ltd, Suite 2A, Basil Chambers, 65 High Street, Manchester, M4 1FS, UK
